Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nazrul-cse-bd (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Spring Boot
RESTful WebServices
Microservices

Nazrul Islam

Fintech | ERP | MFS | Backend Dev | Java | Spring Boot | Senior Software Engineer at Kona Software Lab Ltd. | Entrepreneur Bangladesh

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in JAVA ,Spring Boot, REST, ZMQ, ELK, ORM, JPA, Oracle, MySQL, Angular. Strong engineering professional with a Engineer's Degree focused in Computer Science & Engineering.

Experience

Kona Software Lab Ltd. Senior Software Engineer May 2022 - Present (1 month) Gulshan, Dhaka, Bangladesh

SELISE Digital Platforms Software Engineer March 2022 - May 2022 (3 months) Dhaka, Bangladesh

DataSoft Systems Bangladesh Limited Software Engineer November 2019 - December 2021 (2 years 2 months) Dhaka

Crystal Technology Bangladesh Ltd.
Software Engineer
September 2019 - November 2019 (3 months)

Development & maintaining existing code base of Hospital Management System software based on OpenMRS which is a Govt. project implemented in district level hospitals.

Newgen Technology Limited
Junior Software Engineer
May 2017 - September 2019 (2 years 5 months)

Bangladesh

Education

Jagannath University, Dhaka

M.Sc in Computer Science & Engineering, Computer Science · (2019 - 2020)

Bangladesh Institute of Science & Technology

B.Sc. Hon's Degree, Computer Science & Engineering · (2009 - 2013)